Huh?
I think it's okay for at least one person to
pick up what you're trying to throw away.
So...
Goodbye, Makabe Masamune-kun.
#11 "Face Your Feelings"
Hoshino.
Here.
Honjou.
Makabe.
Makabe's absent again?
Next, Mishima.
Here.
Mutou.
Yaguchi.
Man, Masamune-kun's still absent.
Is this three days now?
Today is the fourth day.
Spring break might start
before he comes back.
Fujinomiya-san, do you know anything?
No... I'm terribly sorry, but I do not.
I've sent him messages,
but he hasn't responded.
He's been ignoring you, too?
Is he so sick that he
can't even get out of bed?
If his condition was that grave,
I don't think our teacher would be
calling his name every morning.
True.
Being absent without permission
for three or four days won't
damage his record, will it?
I'm not sure.
Oh, it's Adagaki-san.
Adagaki-san!
Futaba-san.
Thank goodness. Perfect timing.
Hey, does Masamune-kun have,
like, a cold or something?
A cold?
I mean, he's been absent for four days,
and he hasn't contacted any of us.
Well, that sounds awful.
I hope he's doing all right.
Wait... Did you not know?
I did not. This is the first I've heard of it.
Huh?! B-But you two are dating, aren't you?
No, we've broken up.
What do you mean, Aki-sama?
Exactly what it sounds like.
I broke up with Makabe.
No... But you can't do that!
You can't, Aki-sama!
I don't remember you getting
to decide that for me, Yoshino.
Anyway, it's over now.
There's no point in discussing it further.
You didn't know about those two,
either, Koiwai-san?
Not only did I not know...
This is all a mistake.
A mistake?
After school, I'm going to Pig's Foot's—
to Makabe-kun's house.
To visit him? Then I'll go, too.
M-Me, too!
What about you, Fujinomiya-san?
I'll also go.
I think someone triggered
something they shouldn't have.
Um... Koiwai-san?
But if I can find out the reason,
I'll know how to follow through.
Huh...
So this is what Masamune-kun's
house looks like.
I-It's pretty nice.
I believe that Koiwai-san
and myself have visited before.
What? Really?
It was incredibly awkward.
What do you mean?
I guess now's not the time for that.
Is no one home?
Now that you mention it,
I don't see any lights on.
What?
What should we do with these puddings?
They're super fluffy ones,
made with eggs from the highlands.
Pudding?
Chinatsu-chan?
I smell pudding!
Yeah... Humans definitely
can't live on just school meals.
Thanks for the treat.
They were super delicious!
W-Were they? They're puddings from
a pâtisserie that's all the rage right now.
Are you my brother's friends?
Yet you're this keen on sweets?
Th-Thanks?
Pardon my asking, but has
something happened at home?
Well, my mom's been sorta, uh...
What's in there?
My brother's room.
Oh, sorry. I've been a bit busy.
Mom? I'm coming in.
Whoa. All this stuff to get swole.
I guess that's not surprising
coming from Masamune-sama.
Mom, Onii-chan's friends are here to visit.
Maa-kun? Is that you, Maa-kun?
No, they're Onii-chan's friends.
They brought pudding, too. Do you want some?
No... Maa-kun...
Why did you disappear, Maa-kun?
Gyof.
Waaah! Maa-kun!
Why did you leave me?!
Leave? What does she mean?
My brother ended up going to our grandpa's
place in Shinshu, and he took all his stuff.
What?!
Shinshu?
I guess it wasn't a cold.
He went out last weekend,
and when he came back,
he suddenly wouldn't listen to us.
But I tried! I tried to stop him!
Yes, yes.
As you can see,
Mom's not functioning as a person anymore,
and the chores are just piling up.
I have no idea what's going on.
Last weekend...
Any ideas?
He went on a date with Aki-sama.
Do you think something happened then?
That sounds quite likely.
Maybe Adagaki-san gave him a
really mean nickname or something.
And he decided to run away?
We have no way of getting
through to my brother.
Whether he comes or goes,
he won't listen to what we have to say.
Even though he has all these people
worrying about him now...
My brother really is an idiot.
I'm sorry about this,
after you came to visit...
No, no. I'm sorry we dropped by out of the blue.
It's fine. I think my mom
regained some of her sanity.
We can't get a hold of him,
but if we hear anything, we'll contact you.
Thanks!
We look forward to hearing from you.
Well, that didn't really get us anywhere.
But at least we know where he is now,
even if all we can do is wait.
I think waiting for him is important, too.
Yeah, you're right.
I'll see you later.
Wait for him, huh?
Indeed.
But, man... Shinshu? That's so far.
It certainly doesn't change
the fact that we're worried.
What do you mean by that, exactly?
What are you worried about?
You're actually happy, aren't you?
Koiwai-san?
This is all your fault to begin with.
You got into Aki-sama's head, and now
you got exactly what you wanted.
Hey!
You went out of your way to
do something so underhanded...
Even though Pig's Foot is never
going to look your way anyway.
In that case, wouldn't you say what
you've been doing is also rather deceitful?
Deceitful?
You've known where Masamune-sama's
feelings lay for a long time.
And yet, you ignored them
and sent Aki-sama after him.
Just to protect yourself,
you lied about your own feelings!
My feelings don't matter here!
If this ain't deceit, then what is it?!
You're the biggest coward here!
Who cares about your past
or Adagaki-san's past?!
I have nothing! I have absolutely nothing!
That's enough.
Stop fighting out here.
You'll bother the neighbors.
Futaba-san, I'm sorry, but could
you walk Fujinomiya-san home?
Sure.
Let's have a chat.
Just the two of us. One on one.
I think that should do it.
Oh, look at those flames go.
It's not like staring at a bonfire
is gonna give me any answers...
But I really don't want to think
about anything right now.
I came here when I felt like this as a kid, too.
But this time, I have no one to hate.
So why...
Masamune.
Grandfather.
What's this?
You're not allowed to bring
snacks into this household.
I'm terribly sorry. I wasn't thinking.
I guess burning them doesn't even
create a sweet scent or anything...
Thinking back on everything, I don't think
we've ever had a proper conversation.
Not putting aside that I'm the daughter of
the Adagaki family, and you're the daughter
of the Koiwai family who serves us.
Can we actually put aside
status and talk, though?
I think I thought the same thing, which is
why I never properly acknowledged you.
Even though you've been
right by my side this whole time.
We've done so much together.
We have.
And you've done a lot for me.
I have...
A lot.
I wonder what kind of memories
Aki-sama is remembering.
But this is my job.
It's because I've always relied on you so much
that your only choice was to
kill off your own feelings...
Even though you like Makabe.
You couldn't say that even if you wanted to.
N-No... No, no, no, you're wro—
I'm sorry, Yoshino.
Aki-sama...
It must've been really hard this whole time.
Do you like him?
I just want you to be happy, Aki-sama...
Well, that's something for me to decide.
You don't need to worry about that.
But this is what I decided deep down.
I did something awful that
could never be forgiven, so...
I need to make up for it, at least a little.
But when I spent more time with him...
Contacts
Pig's Foot
I just...
I'm sorry, Aki-sama!
I understand how you feel.
So don't apologize.
This will be the last time
I request something from you.
I want you to properly face your own feelings.
Go. Tell him how you feel yourself.
Okay, Aki-sama.
The next time we see each other,
you can just call me "Aki"!
Karaoke
Vocal Volume
Stability
Technique
Enthusiasm
Rhythm
Points
Comments:
You are a very talented singer!
You're definitely the honor student type.
Calories burned:
Stop Song    to stop              Previous                 Next                  to choose
Preview            Next
You set a new record!
I'm honored.
Now, let's order more drinks!
Futaba-san, thank you for being so considerate.
What are you talking about?
The only ways to heal a broken heart
are overeating and karaoke!
That's common knowledge for girls!
Common knowledge...
Well, I do think I feel a little better.
You know, it wouldn't hurt to
look around you a bit more.
What do you mean?
For example, other classmates...
Like, what about Kojuurou-kyun?
Masamune x Kojuurou,
a.k.a. MasaKoju, is my ship,
but I wouldn't mind sharing him with you.
I can't say I feel anything right now...
I see. I mean, I guess you did love him.
Say, Fujinomiya-san.
If you truly fall in love, there's something
that will always remain with you.
No girl is truly empty inside.
Thank you very much, Futaba-san.
Okay! We should sing this next song together!
Oh, then maybe we should
sing the Hada Pure song.
Okay!
Let's see... Okay, sent!
H-Huh?
That's not it?
What song is this?
Hey... Let me through.
Chinatsu
My grandpa's address is Otari,
Nagano Prefecture...
Hakutaka
Kanazawa
12 cars
Kagayaki
Kanazawa
10 cars
Asama
Nagano
12 cars
Hakutaka
Kanazawa
12 cars
Asama
Nagano
12 cars
Kagayaki
Kanazawa
10 cars
I'm such a shameless liar.
Look at him!
Isn't Makabe Masamune-kun handsome?
When we reunited in high school,
I felt like my breathing might stop.
I decided to see how things
would go before setting a trap,
and the hot guy easily fell for it.
He's such a simpleton.
I still have no regrets about
trying to give that woman
a taste of her own medicine.
And so stubborn at the most awkward times.
Don't get caught up in her pace.
That's not happening.
He doesn't make any sense and he's oblivious.
So...
I never thought my heart would hurt.
I tried to pretend I didn't notice it.
I thought I could.
But...
I think I had the most fun when
I was devising my plan with you.
There was no way I could tell him...
that I had fun, too.
Even so, Aki-sama told me to move forward.
I'm getting off. Please let me through.
Man, this fog is dense.
I guess I'll clean up the firewood.
Gwandfather... I can't run anymo—
That's...
Hey, Little Me.
Hey, Big Me.
Diet and exercise are pretty rough, huh?
Why not run away?
N-No! I can't!
Why's that?
Because I'm gonna get revenge!
Revenge, huh?
That's right! Revenge!
I'm gonna get my revenge and make her pay!
That's why I won't run away!
Listen, Little Me.
She's not your enemy.
The enemy's already been defeated.
Huh?
I'm sure that just sounds like
some pleasantries...
But right now, there are no enemies
in front of me. Not a single one.
So... you don't have to worry.
All your hard work won't go to waste, either.
It might not be exactly how you imagined it...
But you and I will be okay.
Because we just had the
wrong idea about something.
Huh...
This feels weird, but bye.
Yeah, see you later.
Well, guess I'll go for my morning run.
What is that? A tanuki?
Mas...
Master?
Pig's... Foot...
Ow...
Mas—